[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aurora Greenway and Garrett Breedlove were Oscar-winning roles in this movie.", "correct_answer": "Terms of Endearment", "incorrect_answers": ["A Beautiful Mind", "Network", "Shakespeare in Love"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which element was NOT discovered at the University of California in Berkeley, CA, USA?", "correct_answer": "Yb", "incorrect_answers": ["Es", "Fm", "Cf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After they saved their lives The Goonies are seen walking on what beach?", "correct_answer": "Goat Rock State Beach, CA.", "incorrect_answers": ["Rock State Beach, CA.", "Ecola State Park, OR.", "Cannon Beach, OR."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these unusual colors can natural pearls come?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "Green", "Purple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the male lead in the movie Sleepless in Seattle?", "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks", "incorrect_answers": ["Billy Crystal", "Hank Azzaria", "Jason Schwartzman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is heavy water made of ?", "correct_answer": "Two deuterium atoms and one oxygen atom", "incorrect_answers": ["Two hydrogen atoms and two oxugen atoms", "Two oxygen atoms and one hydrogen atom", "Three hydrogen atoms and one oxygen molecule."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Director James Cameron drew all the sketches in Jack Dawsons sketchbook, shown in the film Titanic.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who commissioned  the St. Basils Cathedral?", "correct_answer": "Ivan the Terrible", "incorrect_answers": ["Ivan the Marvelous", "Ivan the Ultimate", "Ivan the Magnificent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The implementation of MPAs is one way to protect the coral reefs from destruction. What does MPA stand for in this context?", "correct_answer": "Marine Protected Area", "incorrect_answers": ["Marine Preservation Act", "Magnetospheric Plasma Analyzer", "Mammal Protection Act"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The highest mountain peak on our planet is Mount Everest. It was first climbed by Edmund Hillary and Tenzing Norgay on May 29, 1953. What is the home country of Sir Edmund Hillary?", "correct_answer": "New Zealand", "incorrect_answers": ["United Kingdom", "The United States", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital city of Iceland?", "correct_answer": "Reykjavik", "incorrect_answers": ["Neyjavicik", "Leykjastick", "Lolymyestic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You should begin the preparation of your meal by mincing a small onion and mixing it with herbs. Then you should saute them in olive oil or this.", "correct_answer": "Unsalted butter", "incorrect_answers": ["Unsalted palm oil", "Unsalted sunflower oil", "Unsalted lard"]}]